I [music]
>> your right now is breaking that neckline
[music]
>> like a rapper
14 hours later
Miami bro content all you too man always
popping up on my screen
>> you seen that purple Bugatti
>> you probably get asked a lot man
>> yeah everybody from this side of the
world is trying buy that car. You know,
this accident happened like at the
beginning of the year. So,
>> let's say that this is one this is one
lane. This is another lane. That's
another lane. I'm in this lane. I go to
this one. And when I go to that final
lane over there, there was a bus. And
when I went into that lane, there's a
1987 Suzuki mini truck.
>> Oh my god. You know what those are,
right?
>> Yeah. He was going like 40 mph with like
these small tail lights. I didn't see
him, but I hit him. He rolled over and
everything, but he's fine.
>> When I seen the Bugette, I'm like,
"Should I buy it? Should I buy it?"
[laughter] And I seen Matt Armstrong. He
was in the comments.
>> Yeah.
>> He's pretty good. I think he'll probably
end up doing that.
>> Yeah. Know, he came to Miami. He checked
it out. Like he saw like it's it's 100%
repairable. The transmission has a
hairline crack.
>> I think it's fine, you know? Like
>> like if if you get that car back for a
million bucks, you wide body it. You
>> Yeah. You do whatever you want to it and
keep it keep it for 10 years,
>> bro. It's worth that money.
>> Keep it for 10 years.
>> All day. It's like money in the bank.
>> Like compared to Miami and Dubai. I
didn't I think it's very similar. I
think it's like everything's super
saturated. Like uruses are like Toyota.
>> Yeah, they're crazy, man.
>> That's why that's why like I came here.
I don't want a Urus. I don't want a
Rolls-Royce. Like I have all that in
Miami. Something low key.
>> I want to lowkey something chill.
>> I know if I go to Miami, I might get
addicted to stuff cuz everyone I ask
that tell me it's Miami is like the buy
but on steroids and you can still do
whatever you want. So here you're
restricted to some things, you know,
Miami.
>> I live in Miami. I was born and raised
in Miami.
>> Whereabouts in Miami? Like what's a good
area?
>> I'll take the Burj Khalifa.
>> Yeah. It's a nice place but too much
traffic.
>> No. Yeah. There's traffic everywhere.
But it just depends your vibe. Like I'm
more of like a poor [__] No, no, no,
no. [laughter] You don't want to go
there. You get shot accidentally.
>> Yeah, you get shot, robbed.
>> I didn't buy, man. They'll offer me all
these places. Fiat Fiana or something
like this.
>> I mean, it's good for the business, but
you're 100% going to get robbed.
>> I I didn't I didn't know you had this
one. What is this?
>> No, the GLS Bravos.
>> Yeah, this one.
>> Yeah, this is the GLS Bravos. This is a
sevenseater. Got like custom uh petrol
blue interior. It's got down exhaust
like
>> H. Yo, this this is some [__] I'll buy
like in Miami. I'm not even going to
lie.
>> Might be blue inside. A little bit
darker though.
>> Okay.
>> So, when we tune this car,
>> I was doing the crapps for too long. I'm
like, bro, like change it. Like, turn it
down a bit.
>> Yeah.
>> You You have this one available?
>> Yeah, I think so. I'll check the check
the list. I'll check the sold.
>> Yeah. No, like to Miami. We'll take it
to Miami.
>> Take the [laughter] Bro,
>> look. This is like glass. It's very
nice. Bro, I just don't want to be
another one of these rental guys with
like Lamborghinises and Ferraris. Like,
that's just so played out. They done
[__] up.
>> Put it closer.
>> Oh, [__]
[music]
[__] 10 days. We're just trapped in
this building, bro.
>> Explain that story.
>> Uh, I don't know if I want to explain
the story. Let's just say our first time
coming to Dubai. We were uneducated,
unguided, and uh we were stuck in the
wrong hotel for way too long, like 10
days. [snorts] That was bad. I gained
like 20 lbs. Bro, remember that [__]
>> You have Alex G as your mentor
when you have other gurus as your
mentor.
[laughter]
>> Yeah, we were all fat during that time.
>> Wagging burger, the ice cream, and what
was the other [__]
Hookah every bro. That was so bad. Yo,
we just saw a whole pack of camels, bro.
Wild camels, bro. They were way closer
to the highway, dude.
>> Oh, you see them?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Where?
>> Oh, we're going to run up on them. Yo,
I'm going to leave the car right here,
bro. I don't [__]
>> But why don't we just drive to them?
>> I don't This [__] might get stuck.
[__] bro.
It's stuck, bro. That's exactly what I
[__] said, dude.
>> Whatever. We'll just go get the camera.
We'll figure this [__] out later.
[laughter]
>> Yo, you know what? I've actually now I
realize I've never actually been
>> in the desert.
>> In the desert.
>> It's not much.
>> Told you. I'm not [__] crazy.
>> Some wild came.
>> Damn, bro. I'm not going to lie. They're
a lot bigger in person. They're closer
to me. This feels illegal to Well, if it
feels illegal, it probably is illegal
here. Well,
>> that is what the guy told us. Not a guy.
According to him, these are his camels.
He just said
that's all he said. [music]
[music]
Where the [__] is the car?
>> This car. No,
>> no,
>> no.
>> Coming my friend and uh money.
>> Yeah. No. Dirham
>> credit.
>> Credit card.
>> Credit card. No 100.
>> Yeah, 100 did.
>> Cash is king. Cash talks any language.
>> Big facts.
>> But I feel like I could pull it out.
I said a little
>> Thank you, brother.
>> We have been in Dubai for the last two
days. Probably like the first day and a
half has just been pure jet lag. So, for
the first time in my life, I took
melatonin and I fell asleep as soon as I
got onto the plane. I had a lay down
flat seat. I laid down on the seat. I
knocked out and then some lady came up
to me and and went, "Hey, uh, Mr.
Gonzalez." I'm like, "Yeah, yeah, what
happened?" He's like, "Um, sir, the last
portion to deboard the plane. We're in
Dubai." I'm like, "What the [__] What
do you mean we're in Dubai?" I fell
asleep the whole [__] flight. I
missed breakfast, lunch, and dinner. My
$20,000 ticket that I paid to be in
first class was completely pointless
because uh didn't enjoy it. I just fell
asleep throughout the whole flight and
figure how long I fell asleep. I didn't
even take a picture to post on social
media. That was an L. Can't write it off
anymore, right? But we're in Dubai, so
we're going to be here in Dubai for the
next 2 weeks, maybe 3 weeks. We have a
big trading expo happening next week. We
decided to come a week early. Have a
couple of friends that we want to meet
up with and just hang out with. I have a
lot of friends on this side of the world
that I've actually never met. So, right
now we're actually going to go hit the
gym at the five palm. Well, not at the
five palm. We're going to go hit the gym
at the outdoor gym in front of the five
palm. Um, we haven't worked out since we
got here. We pretty much just been
sleeping all of these days. I'm learning
a little bit of uh
Saudi language.
>> What's something you've learned?
>> Oh, what was the other thing that I
learned?
Um,
hold your heart. [laughter]
>> Yeah, [music]
cuz [__] started talking to me like
I'm slowing down. Opinions over
statistics, of course.
Gassed [music] off journalistic coming
me and all you'll get is the ballistic
report. Book a private [music] room at
Wallally's way of twist in the court.
Sometimes you got to just walk it off,
you know. Yo, yo, look for all you
[__] that say I don't have
legs. Ready? What is that?
>> Who says that?
>> I get tried sometimes, bro. See, I don't
got legs. Look at this.
>> I don't know who be trying you. You
obviously have women legs.
>> Wait, what? You said I have women leg.
Want to see what else I have? Not Not
much. Not right now. You see,
you know what's funny? I think about was
it like a year and a half ago?
>> Yeah.
>> Maybe 2 years ago was my first time
coming to Dubai and I just came to work
with my team. to have a lot of guys on
this side of the world. Everybody's visa
can just meet here. And I rented this
villa for about I think it was like 7
days and we were all inside this house
just like planning our year. And all I
can say is that we exceeded what we had
planned for the year by three times.
Pretty trippy. Like like we planned 2024
[music]
entirely inside of there and half of
2025. Now it's ending in 2025. We're
back but with a bigger plan. Stay tuned.
We didn't even go to the
>> Yeah, we didn't we didn't even know that
there was a club here and we didn't go
once because
it's very different to what we're used
to. All right, boys. I'm so excited. I
very rarely get excited for stuff. But
today, we're going to be deep diving in
the world's deepest pool. Huge.
Can they Can they even see or no?
>> I see my reflection, bro. Oh, look.
Looks right now.
I don't know if you guys know, but I I
actually have been free diving for like
10 years. So, I'm Cuban and my family
has always gone out in the water with a
boat and we've always free dive, scuba
dive, spear fished. Today, my goal is to
do 25 m, which is like 60 70 ft. Free
dive just straight straight. I can hold
my breath for like 4 minutes. It's one
of my special powers. Free diving here
is going to be so easy cuz there's no
current. There's no krill. So, krill is
I sound like a nerd right now. Kills
like the kills like these micro shrimp
in the ocean that are literally
everywhere when you deep dive and they
make a noise in your ears whenever you
dive and they they create more density
in the water. There's none of that here.
It's just straight fresh water. But I'm
so excited. Hopefully I don't [__]
pass out. And
you ruin the trip.
>> Yeah, that that'll suck.
On my way to [__] your [__]
I'm not going to lie, it's just tight as
hell.
Like it's like
the scene from Spider-Man when he's
taking on like the black version of
himself.
>> I'm so excited.
I'm so excited. When I pass out, I don't
make the pass to my leisure is
under the sea.
Under the sea,
darling, it's better down where it's
wet. Take it from me.
I'm [music] sure they work all day. I'll
bring the sun away while we devoting
full time to floating under the sea. Ha!
I did 25 m. That was not easy at all.
>> That was awesome, bro. I feel so
confident, dude. I feel like a [__]
dolphin, bro. I feel like a [__]
mermaid. Like, no one can [__] with me,
bro.
>> Yes. Yes. He He needs help. He needs
help. Yes. Yes. Pull. Pull. Pull. Yes.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Hard. Hard. Pull it hard.
Yes, this is I think I got [laughter]
it.
>> That's where I got stuck to each side.
>> Thank you very much. That was awesome.
Oh my god. Hot as [__] All right, boys.
Now, what do we do now?
>> Probably go eat. Get some protein. and
go get some protein.
[__] with me.
>> Um, I feel like a guru in here. I'm in
Dubai. I feel like this is the perfect
place to break down the trade. All
right, so following up on a breakdown
from EuroUSD that I just did. My goal
this week is to make a million dollars
and show you guys the exact same trades
I'm taking so you guys can replicate it
and follow along. And why am I so
confident for this week? Well, because
I'm in Dubai and trading London session
cannot be easier. Right now, it is the
prime time of London session. In Miami,
where I usually trade, it would be 1:00
a.m. It's 9:00 in the morning. I'm going
to be awake all day watching the trades.
Like, what? So, let me show you guys
these trade setups right now. My first
trade is going to be Euro USD. I'm going
to be waiting for price to break below
this neckline in order for us to take
the sell to the downside. Next, we have
AUDUSD, which I'm probably going to be
interested in entering this trade maybe
in the next 1 hour to 30 minutes. I want
to see if this candlestick could engulf
in the next 20 minutes. We'll take this
trade to the upside. And then last but
not least, it's going to be Euro GBP for
a counter trend trade. Waiting for this
trade to have a reaction from this left
head, right shoulder, retesting the
neckline and having a push to the
downside. This right here is an absolute
beauty. Euro USD right now is breaking
that neckline to perfection. So, we are
having that beautiful continuation push
to the downside. I anticipate for us to
come back and not retest this neckline
and continue having a push down, but I'm
very very bearish on this trade. AUDUSD
is having a beautiful push to the
upside. We are having a very strong
rejection and continuation bullish
engulfing to the upside and Euro GBP.
Look at this massive [__] bearish
engulfing rejecting from this left head,
right shoulder retest neckline.
Beautiful sell to the downside. Bucking
three for three and it's only been an
hour and a half. So, right now we're on
our way to the FX Expo and it's my first
time ever coming to a convention center
like this out of the country and I
thought it'd be a very cool experience,
network with other, you know,
entrepreneurs, other traders, big
ballers out here, big big big traders,
and just get to meet other people, show
them the trades that I'm in right now,
how I just broke them down a couple
hours ago, and just see what happens.
So, it's a two-day event. I'm very late.
I was supposed to be here at 9:00 in the
morning. I was trading, so that was a
priority and, you know, recording this
for you guys. So let's uh let's see how
it goes.
>> This is just unexpected meeting guys.
Unexpected. Nice to meet you, bro. Nice
to meet you.
>> Wait, are you coming you're coming from
India?
>> Yeah. Yeah, we came from India. In India
there's a huge craze about you.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. A lot of people like each and
every Indian sees you and they know each
and everything about you. I literally
first came when I see I asked him like
is this literally you? [laughter]
Nice to meet you. Nice to meet you.
>> Thank you very much for you from here.
>> I love [__] Indian. [laughter]
>> I love I love Indian screen is not this
is not visible trading [__]
Indian.
>> Turn on me [__] live chat man.
[laughter]
>> Thank you very much for being available
on the YouTube and on internet man.
You're like you are an inspiration. All
right, boys. Update right now on the
trade. So, Euro GDP has officially hit
take profit. Finally, that was, bro, I
don't even I think like 3 4 hours we
finally hit our take profit. Euro USD
right now is currently very nice to
profit. Very 4 hours strong closure. So,
right now it is 6:00 in the morning
Miami time. So, I'm currently like
uploading stories right now like on
Instagram. I'm doing everything live,
but the Wi-Fi in here sucks. Too many
people in here. Right now, we're up
about $400,000, $440,000 more or less.
job is not finished until we're not at a
million dollars. I'm not going to lie,
this went a lot faster than I expected.
Usually my trades take longer to go into
profit. I am not complaining about a
trade giving me a 1 to2 risk of reward
in 4 hours. This is the beauty of
trading in these sessions. Like usually
I would wake up to some [__] like this
and now obviously what's happening is
what's going on?
>> How you doing? How are you? I've been
following you all for a long time.
>> Yeah. Yeah. on the Instagram 5 years
I've seen you under to a million horse.
>> Yeah, we're we're in a Oh, [__] bro.
The Wi-Fi is not working. Oh, look.
There you go.
>> Oh, come on. Exact same. Oh, exact same
position.
>> Yeah, you're in the same position.
>> Exact same position.
>> Oh, [laughter] [__]
>> Oh, wait, wait, wait, look. Right here.
Right here.
>> Bang. Bang. Same position.
>> Exact same. Yeah.
>> Where's your TP?
>> Okay. So, I don't have a TP. I just set
and forget.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Wait, but so did you actually trade off
of what I posted?
>> Trade myself. Perfect. Where's your
Where's your entry at?
>> So, my entry is Euro USD cuz I'm on Euro
USD and your GP.
>> Yeah, I sent you USD trade. Uh I had
this from last Friday, but
>> Oh, but you got a better entry than I
did. I I entered a little bit lower.
>> I was going to break that consolidation
box.
>> All right, that's sick. [laughter]
>> There you go. I'm
>> That's what I'm talking about. This has
a lot more potential. This should be
like 800,000 more or less. Like,
>> I mean, you said it, right? You called
it as always. So,
>> wait. So, you saw me break down the
trade on Instagram live like you saw.
>> Of course. Of course, brother.
>> I know.
>> We always see you and then you just like
follow whatever you say.
>> You set and forget and that's it.
>> I just want to ask you one question.
Okay.
>> About your course.
>> Okay.
>> Okay. But I still haven't made any money
yet. Like can you like can you show me a
live trade? Is that possible? A live
trade?
>> Bro, people are going to think this is
fake, bro. This is fake.
>> Is it a live one?
>> What?
>> It's the Wi-Fi. Let it got to give it a
second.
Can you go on the Can you go on the
broker?
>> Floating 400.
>> Many people say you're a scammer. So,
but I don't believe it. Okay.
>> Many people say it. So,
>> wait. Wait. I don't know.
>> Okay. Okay.
>> Bro's legit. Bro, [laughter]
>> legit. Bro, legit.
>> 2 million on the live. Floating P&L.
>> Is that a lot?
>> No. Not much.
>> Okay. I just want to make sure. I don't
>> like it's not a lot. If I'm India,
>> it's a lot.
>> All right. Let's give it a second.
>> It's like a cheap hat from the comments.
>> Let's Let's see the real money.
>> Okay. So, this like the trade's live,
right? Like I'm in this trade. So I'm
>> You're still on Euro.
>> Yeah. I'm literally posting it right now
on my Instagram while people are
watching it. Like I'm literally
following it right now.
>> What did you short on?
>> Yeah. So look, this student right here
look
in my community just posted 1 hour ago
and he also caught the trade and he made
$22,000
right now.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Look, it's a it's a closed
position right here. Look I'm literally
as you speak, you walked up to me as I
was taking a screenshot of this trade
right here.
>> All right. So you must have a hell of
screenshots.
>> That's what I was doing right now. Yeah.
At what point is best to take partial
profits?
>> Never. You never Yeah, you never take
partials. You only take um No,
>> because you trade such a huge, you know,
capital. You still don't take partial no
I I only close I only close full
position.
>> Yeah. I have a question. Okay. Before
you did this thing like you play rock
your business and you have $10,000.
>> So So can you still do it
>> or
>> you have $10,000?
>> I'll give you like a line of credit for
1 year, 6 months, 600.
>> If we're going to bet $10,000, you have
to have 10,000.
>> That's true. That's true. So we get Oh,
what is this? Do you want black and red?
>> Okay. Okay. Uh,
>> black.
>> Black.
>> Ah,
>> right. No worries.
>> Credit 10,000.
>> Just share me your WhatsApp number. So,
you know,
>> guys, nice meeting you,
>> bro. It's actually amazing, guys.
>> I see you're not a scammer anymore.
>> Huh?
>> Of course, I'm not a scammer, bro. I'm
right here.
But many people thinking about but you
are not scammers.
>> So I'm approved by the Indian community
that I not [laughter]
Indian people.
>> Okay. Thank you brother. Appreciate it
guys. See you guys. Amazing.
>> Way to prove by the Indian community
[laughter]
brother.
>> Oh my god. [laughter]
Good to see you. Yeah,
>> I I'm you know on this stage where I've
crossed that looking at chart every time
>> when I have time I analyze not making
money but not losing money anymore.
Yeah.
>> So risk management everything it's been
1 and a2 years now it's proper.
Hopefully by 1 year 2 year like
graduation 3 years
>> I'll be making money. Yeah.
>> I just wanted one picture from
just pictures.
You
>> do not know me. I'm from South Africa.
>> Nice to meet you.
>> I I wish I saw you in Cape Town. I
remember there was a time you came to
Cape Town but I I stay in. So, um, yeah,
right. It's an honor to meet you.
>> Pleasure, brother.
>> I'm glad you you redid the 100 to a
million.
>> Okay.
>> Yeah, cuz the first time. Yeah,
>> I failed. Yeah, I failed.
>> But I'm glad I'm glad you redid it, man.
You you're you're a hero. And one day I
will be like you.
>> Yes, you are. Appreciate it, brother.
Thank you, man. They gave me.
>> All right. So, this right here, this is
my long lost brother. So, let me give
you guys a backstory on who KO is. So,
>> you want to tell them? Tell them the
story. Yeah, it was basically in 2021 we
met Instagram. I just make life and this
guy join.
>> So 2021 I I have small Instagram.
>> Yes.
>> I think I have like 100 followers couple
of hundred
>> like 100 followers and then he is on IG
live couple thousand people right IG
live and then he's like yo who wants to
go live? I request it and he accepts it.
And that's like when I started becoming
a profitable trader and we've been like
online friends for like 5 years and we
finally meet in person.
>> Yes. I can't believe it guys.
>> It was very difficult. I always tell for
this guy I'm going to m but some reason
the life stopped me. So but yeah now
finally we're here.
>> It's time to make some money.
>> He gave me this. This is going to my
house. So brother I appreciate um
that's what I get for flexing on
Instagram. 314,000.
Let's go home. All right, bro. You need
to you need to tell them what you just
told me earlier again.
>> All right, that you made me hella money.
>> No, but say it how you say it again.
Like
>> it was it was natural, man. I can't fake
it. I can't fake it. You can act it.
I'll try.
>> Okay, go.
>> Yeah. Yeah, I'll try. But I can't just
>> No, just go do it. Go.
>> Alex, you made me hell of money, man. I
[__] love you, bro. You know how much
money you made me?
>> How much?
>> I don't know, man. I lost count when I
reached 30,000. That's exactly how he
came out to me earlier.
>> You did make me a lot of money. I see
you post something, I full that [__]
[laughter] It's Alex, you know, it's
you, you know.
[music]
All right, boys. So, we're back for day
two. I wasn't going to come today for
day two, but I said, "You know what? All
of my Indian people are here. We had a
such a [__] good time yesterday that
I need to come again today. I need to
meet the people cuz I I I didn't say
that I was coming yesterday. I just
pulled up and I just posted like when I
was leaving, bro. I think I got 3,000
DMs that people were going to pull up
today if I were to just pull up." And
like, if I'm on this side of the road, I
want to meet you guys. So, I said, "Fuck
it. I'm just pulling up." Not letting
them know I'm here. Trade update.
Today's looking pretty decent. So
yesterday we had a retracement back into
the retest of this neckline. Euro GBP
still in profit as we speak. Trade right
now is uh 300K.
>> I'm from India.
Big fan of
>> Good to see you here.
>> Yeah, bro. I'm excited, bro. I'm
excited.
>> When you told me you're here, the voice
I didn't even know you were like a main
sponsor for this either. uh Forex.
[laughter]
>> I'm not
>> I want to do something with like a tiger
or something like
>> Tell me. You said you let me know.
>> Yeah. Like I'm safe, right? It's not
going to
>> like worse comes like a little no.
>> No, that's right. It's good. Okay, we
can do it tomorrow.
>> Wednesday? Yeah. I saw you for trading.
I was like,
>> he's doing a million dollar. Bro, you
need to do the challenge with the
million. I want to make a million
dollars.
>> Right now, right now I'm up.
>> Oh my god.
>> Is this going to lower? You're up 300 or
100 356.
>> Oh my god. Yeah. Yeah. So like I was up
half a mill yesterday, but I'm up
>> He's up He's up $350,000.
>> But I lost 150 grand. I'm like making it
back, man. I'm trying. Yeah. Like if
this drink closes in profit, I'll be
like 800.
>> By the way, you got the watch.
>> Oh yeah. Black and red. Black.
>> Black or red. I'm not playing for money.
I'm not playing for money. No chance.
>> Wait for the color.
>> Okay. Red. Red. Red. You sure?
>> Yeah.
>> Guys,
>> we're here doing stuff. Right. Wow.
>> $50 million, guys. I just wanted to Oh,
[__] That's crazy.
>> Thanks for the free tip today. This
week.
>> Oh, yeah. I'm in the sales. Yeah. Still
made money.
>> I held it. Diamond hands.
>> Set and forget.
>> Nice.
>> Making money.
>> The man himself.
>> I see. [laughter]
>> That's the man right there, man.
>> So, this is one of my most profitable
students. We did podcast one. We did a
podcast, too. I gave you the 10,000.
>> Yeah.
>> How's it going? I I haven't seen it.
>> All right, cool. We I'll give you a
breakdown of it. I'll give you a
breakdown.
>> Wait, wait, wait. So, people get more
context. People get more context. So, I
did a podcast with him a year ago. No,
like 2 years ago.
>> Yeah, about a year and a half ago.
>> A year and a half ago. And I'm like, yo,
if you make X percentage in I think it
was 6 or 12 months, whatever.
>> Now, you gave me 2 months. You said any
amount of profits in 2 months.
>> 6 months.
>> I'll give you 10,000. Exactly. So, he
made like crazy 120% whatever. So then
we do another podcast and then I give
him the 10,000 and now we meet here in
person.
>> Got good news and bad news. Yeah. I
smashed my phone this morning, man.
>> Sorry. I was there the other day.
>> Oh yeah. I'm in those trades as well. By
the way,
>> yo, show show.
>> All right. Let me show you probably. So
this one's my FTMO.
>> Okay. So you're in the same Euro USD USD
USD CF. I've been on this for about 4
days, bro. I went through the [__] I I
got in a bit early. You know what I
mean?
>> Um but the actual account All right,
cool. So let me break it down to you.
Let me break it down to you. First
trade. So, I thought initially,
>> what do you what do you think right now
about Euro USD?
>> Oh, bro, hold that, man. Hold [laughter]
that. I swear I'm waiting for that to do
a heavy drop.
>> Heavy.
>> Oh, it's happening right now live, bro.
Look,
>> crazy cuz that shit's moving like Yo,
it's moving as we speak right now.
>> You know what's happening? That's going
to keep going. That's just going to keep
going, man. Oh my god, bro. I didn't
even realize.
>> Oh, check it. All right. Look. No, wait.
Wait. Wait for it. 450. All right.
>> I got
>> All right, boys. So, we are here to buy
[laughter] so random. We're here to buy
our second Jacob and Co roulette. We're
going to have this one with a red strap
and then we're going to have this one
with a green strap. So, Kimbo roulette,
>> bro. Having two of these is going to be
crazy.
>> Yeah. No, weird. It's hard.
>> Different for sure.
>> This ball looks like it moves faster
than this one.
>> Oh, wait. Look, the ball on this one is
is smaller. You see it?
>> Like the ball is tinier. This ball is
bigger.
>> Okay.
>> Maybe like the year difference or
something. I don't know. What's this
one?
>> Same thing. Same year. Oh, 2024.
>> So, it's 2025.
>> 11 out of 101. Yeah. This is sick. All
right. What do you guys want to do?
>> What was that? What number was that?
>> 71. It would have been cool if they were
like 112 or something, but yeah.
>> Okay. So, do you want to explain what
we're doing right now?
>> All right. So, basically, we're going to
So, we're going to flip. Well, spin
>> spin
>> for 1,000 difference or 2,000
difference. What was the difference?
>> Fouls. What?
>> 1,000 difference. Was a foul.
>> Okay. So, we're spinning for 1,000 right
now to see who wins. What color do you
want to pick?
>> I'll leave it up to you.
>> I got black for black. So, let's go.
[laughter]
Black for black.
>> All right.
>> You want to do it on the black watch or
the red one? The black watch.
>> Let's go for the black watch. I'll let
you spin it.
>> This is too many odds against us here.
I'm not going to lie.
>> All right. Spinning it.
Damn. This one spins way more than mine.
I'm not going to lie.
>> It's not black, bro.
>> It's a smaller ball, so it goes more.
>> It's going to land on green.
and
red. [laughter]
>> Thank you, man. Appreciate you. We got
this, bro. Sick.
>> All right. Well, now
>> I just left that out here with another
free one on the other wrist, you know.
>> Oh, let me down, man. I didn't think it
would.
>> All right, boys. Trade update. We just
left. We got I feel like feel like a
rapper.
>> Just making a a wangster gangster.
>> All right, so trade up there right now.
Euro USD is having a continuation push
to the downside. looking very very
solid. AUD/USD, we avoided this loss to
perfection. So, this trade was avoided
and Euro GBP is having a major
retracement. So, not going to lie,
pretty big L on my end right here for
not closing this trade down over here.
So, we would be up so much more right
now. We would be up 275 here plus 250
that I was up on this one. We'd be up
like 600 grand right now. But, I decided
to get greedy and continue to hold this
one. This is a counter trend trade. So,
this trade we did not anticipate for it
to make it all the way back, you know,
like this is like we're supposed to be
buying here basically. And uh we still
decided to continue to hold this trade
has so much more downside potential. We
will continue to hold this position. And
that right there shows you boys got to
have [__] balls. Balls of [__]
steel. Two big [__] balls to
hold the [__] trade through some draw
down, a little bit of a retracement.
Yesterday, put on my Twitter, right? I'm
not a big Twitter guy, but I just uh I
literally just put everything out here
on Twitter. Um, what the hell did I put?
Everybody was asking me, "Yo, Alex, what
do I do with the trade?" I said, "Alex,
what do we do now?" I said, "Set and
forget." That was a trade before
yesterday. 50,000 people saw that live.
That's a trade now.
Set and forget.
>> And then I did this other tweet and it's
kind of funny cuz some people when they
come to me in person, they're like, "Yo,
Alex, you're actually a really nice guy.
Like, I don't know why. I thought I
thought you'd be a dickhead." Like, why
would you think I'm a [__] I mean,
I and I and and I read this tweet that I
posted. I'm like, well, I can see how I
can come off a little arrogant
sometimes, but I do it because I just
don't I hate arguing with small-minded
people in the industry, honestly. To me,
it's a [__] waste of time. So, I said
here, "Hater, love me. I called the
moves. Simple. Call a demo money if you
want. I'll be withdrawing my demo funds
and eating waggy." Said for Okay, fine.
It's a little arrogant, but it always be
it always be the the the the the
non-believers, the haters that are the
ones saying it's demo, it's real, it's
not fake. Okay, let's let's say the
trades let's say I'm trading demo. [__]
it. All right, I'm trading demo. You
caught me. Cool. Can you at least give
me credit that I'm predicting the
trades? Am I not literally saying that
the trade is going to go from this point
to this point and then to continue to
hold? Do you just think I'm going to
predict this and not actually risk money
behind it? In what [__] right mind
does that make sense? That's why I don't
argue with small-minded people. And uh
we set up and forget them. I'm about to
close out my biggest profits in a single
day for $738,000.
Now, before I close this trade out live
right now, I think it's so much cooler
than me making money that I just shared
this on social media 2 days ago and tens
of thousands if not hundreds of
thousands of people were able to
capitalize off of this just off of a
[__] Instagram video. Yo, generally
speaking, if you guys make money off of
this trade, comment it down below.
anything. If you guys were to actually
if you guys even saw this happen in real
time and you guys followed it and you
guys edited it, just comment it. You
guys have no idea how much that
motivates me and it keeps me going to
just continue to do this for you guys.
So, let's close out my biggest profits
in a single day here together. So, we're
going to go to bulk operations and we're
going to close oppositions.
Bang. [laughter]
>> Hopefully, you make it back to America
alive, you know.
Tigers,
>> bro, you're going to go play with
tigers. I don't know if
>> we'll do the friendly approach
[laughter] first. First we'll do the
safe stuff, then we do, you know.
>> Yeah, we better be safe all the time.
>> [__] [laughter] way,
>> bro. You see, you're strong, too.
>> Like one on this side, one on this end.
What if I don't like Oh, they're pretty
aggressive, bro. I'm not going to lie.
>> Yeah. Ah,
>> they're smart. They're smart.
>> You have to lure them. They're like
women. You feed them, then you touch
them. [laughter]
>> [laughter]
>> Yo, this [__] is so high off the ground,
bro. [music]
[music]
>> Did it freeze or it's slowly coming
down? Holy [__]
>> it's on bags.
>> Yo, that was the craziest up and down
ever.
Hi, brother.
>> Yeah, that's you, bro.
>> No, that's you first.
>> Honestly, I don't like doing this, so
I'd rather you go in first,
>> bro. This is one of those things. It's
good till uh he wants to eat you. I feel
like you're being too friendly with
them. I would
>> No, this is like a
>> It's a four-way right here. [laughter]
>> Oh, that's so cute.
>> Why is he casually walking?
>> Guys, we need the poo.
>> Hey, this is walking a bit. If he bites,
do not pull. Okay.
>> Don't leave him like this.
>> Yeah. Don't pull.
>> He will bite.
>> And if he bites, do not pull.
>> Don't pull when he bites.
>> Bro, I This is stronger than my dog,
>> bro. [laughter]
>> Okay. Yo, Alex, you got it, right?
>> Yeah. I I What if he comes at me?
>> Yo, the tongue is hurting when he's
licking cuz it has the spikes.
>> Oh, my socks.
>> Oh, no.
>> My shoe. Chicken. Chicken. Chicken.
Okay.
>> Yeah, chicken.
>> Oh.
Oh, [laughter]
>> it's so strong, bro.
>> Hell no.
>> Oh, hell no. [laughter]
>> He's trying to wrestle you.
>> No, no, no, bro. Why does it look like
he's coming at me?
>> Holy [__] [laughter] bro. He's so
strong. You might want to take off that
one.
>> Oh, okay. Okay. I I thought I knew.
>> This guy is the best.
What's this?
>> I got one. [laughter]
>> This is the queen.
>> She owns you tonight.
>> Like you.
>> She like me.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> She does. [laughter]
[laughter]
>> Kill me.
360.
Hey. Huga. Stop.
She really likes him.
>> She's attracted to you. So if he catch
you, she cannot leave you now.
>> She She like you guys. No, no, no.
>> Wait. So she likes me now.
>> Yes.
>> She really wants you. Look, look, look,
look, look, look. [laughter]
>> It's not me. It's him. I know you don't
want me, but I'm all you have.
>> Oh,
>> no. All right. You cannot change like
this.
>> Go.
>> Don't do that.
>> I don't mind. I'm just scared that she'd
grab me and like me really strong.
>> I don't think she'll kill you.
>> No, she's fine.
>> She will not hug you is too strong. But
to
[laughter]
>> What else? What else?
>> Uhhuh. What were you saying?
>> What were you saying?
>> I'm talking one more.
>> Baba.
>> Baba. [laughter]
>> Good news is we made it out alive.
>> Bad news is Alex uh broke up with his
love, you know.
>> That was hella weird. I'm not going to
lie. But that was pretty cool. That was
good.
>> Honestly, I've been there a few times. I
never knew they get attached like that.
Couple little scratches, no big deal.
Little battle wounds. It's all good, you
know. It is what it is.
>> We made it, guys.
>> I have a big head. I have a lot of
brain. [laughter] I have a lot of brain.
>> It's all that trading. It's all that
trading, you know. It's expanding.
>> Now, now we need the headpiece.
>> Now we talking.
[laughter]
>> Okay. So, so this is supposed to stay
like this. Okay.
>> Now you look like a Bugatti owner.
>> 100%.
>> Now this is the guy who owns a Bugatti.
[laughter]
Mo Mo Mo Mo Mo Mo Mo Mo Mo Mo Mo Mo Mo
Mo Mo Mo Mo Mo Mo Mo Mo just got me my
first bit.
>> You're now you're now official.
>> Thank you very much.
>> Welcome to Dubai.
>> We're walking around like this, man.
>> All right, boys. So, we've been here a
week already in Dubai and you know, we
don't have a flight back and I haven't
found a reason to leave and uh my cars
are currently in the shop in Miami and I
just sold my Mansory Cullinin. I'm like,
wait, there's Mansory in Dubai. Let's
see if we can buy something mansery
here. So, I'm talking to Mo Vlogs and
he's like, yo, I actually know Mr.
Mansery himself and like I know his son.
like, "Holy [__] can can we go meet
them because uh I think that'd be
extremely cool. Maybe I can actually
take a car back to Miami." Fun fact, I
actually got subpoenenaed by Mansury
themselves. Mansur sent me a lawsuit for
my blue G Wagon basically cuz I I said,
"Oh, I bought a Mansury G Wagon." And
then supposedly it was a fake G Wagon.
And then I get sued. I'm like, "Well,
what the fuck?" So, I'm sure it wasn't
Mr. Mansury himself or his son. I think
that it was, you know, one of the
franchises, but we're going to we're
going to confront him right now and be
like, "Mr. answering. Why the [__] did
you sue me? Like, [laughter] you know.
>> Hello, bro.
>> What's up, my brother? How are you? Good
to see you, Alex.
>> This is Kuros Mansuri. Nice to meet you.
>> That's his actual name. Kuros Mansuri.
>> How you doing? Good.
>> Welcome, man. Good. And you? This is
sick, bro.
>> Yeah.
>> I've had a I've had a couple of your
cars like Mansuri cars
>> in the US.
>> In the US. Yeah.
>> Gas.
>> I had a Yeah, I got I got sued for that
one.
>> You know why?
>> 100%. I know. Yeah. I got I had that
one. kind of had a had a real cullin and
manory and a couple of other cool parts.
[music]
>> Seeing them here in person is very
different from videos.
>> Yeah, you can check the quality if you
don't I see you have one. If you see it
here, you see a big difference.
>> Oh, yeah. You you can feel the
difference in like the like the steering
wheel.
>> Yeah, you do.
>> In the back, you have more space here.
Enough space.
>> How did you how did you guys extend it?
>> The big job. You have to cut the car and
make the everything longer from the
exhaust, the cabling, the axis,
everything you have to extend.
>> What was what was something like this?
>> This is 4.5
>> dirham.
>> Yeah.
>> So like a million US.
>> Yeah. It's a bit over a million.
>> Wow.
>> That's serious.
>> Yeah.
>> What's this? Like what's what's this
exactly?
>> This is a Porsche 92 turbos with the
full package.
>> You can tell the difference in between
like the Miami stuff and this.
>> Like it's like like
>> it's like not flappy.
>> Of course. Of course. It's like very
like, you know, all of Miami is full of
fake everything.
>> Yeah, I know.
>> Like just like knockoff versions of her.
>> We're going to change soon.
>> We were just talking about it right now.
If I buy back my Bugatti from auction,
how long would it take for you guys to
build the Mansur like one of one
everything?
>> Um,
half a year maybe.
>> And then you need the car to be here?
>> No, in Germany. We're based in Germany.
>> So the factories, everything is in
Germany.
>> So we have to ship it to Germany.
>> Yeah. The best thing is if we ship the
car to Germany and then we ship it back.
That would be a crazy but like fully
exposed carbon. I don't know. Like what
do you make?
>> Wow.
>> Just some crazy custom interior like
Tiffany blue or something. That would be
sick. I'm not going to lie.
>> I'm getting excited. I hear that. I'm
getting excited. I better be there to
see this being made. That's all I want.
[laughter]
>> That's crazy.
>> The thing is that we have to figure out
how we buy it back from the auction
because now a lot of people from from
here from UAE want to buy the car cuz if
the car comes here, it's clean type.
Sell me something. Sell me something. I
need to buy some.
>> Let's go to the other section with cars.
[laughter]
>> The mascar one. Same as on the arm
watch.
>> You can take this out.
>> I can take it out. I have one mom vlog.
>> It's one of 25. I guess it says on the
dome.
>> This is number 10. This is number 71 out
of 101. I love numbers though. Okay. So,
>> 5K.
>> 5K. Let's go. Let's take it. [laughter]
>> Wait. Five. Uh,
>> 5K. Yeah.
>> Dirhammer.
>> US.
>> US. Okay. I'll take
>> Oh, I have to check.
>> E. Okay, let's go. I'll take it.
>> I get fake.
>> This This is a This is a a super sport,
right?
>> It's a Chiron. B Chiron.
>> Yeah. Chiron Super Sport or
>> No, it's a B Chiron.
>> Bay Shiron. Oh,
>> but the fit for all cars because we
changed the full front bumper to full
front.
>> How much is this?
>> The skate.
>> Oh, cuz you don't you don't sell this.
>> You mean the the the model or the car?
>> This like let's say I want to take this.
>> Sell it for I guess 3,000 D. I'll take
this. I'll give it to you.
>> Yeah, I'll take this.
>> Thank you very much. This is amazing.
Set forget. This is sick.
>> Yeah, it's like the biggest demo I've
ever seen in my life. I've seen it like
I've been invited to a couple buildings,
but nothing like this.
It's
>> like 20 ft tall.
[laughter]
>> So, they create like a This is pretty
crazy how they do this. I thought that
was a real view for a second.
>> This is just some of our general like
two-bedroom apartments, right? So,
that's
>> kitchen and and the layout. This is like
100 m uh penthouse. Floor to ceiling
here is only 2.9. So you can imagine
what the 4.2 is going to
>> double. It's double.
>> Yeah. Almost. Yeah.
>> This is going to be very very very
different here.
>> Yeah.
>> You're excited.
>> Yeah. Very much so. Yeah. I love it.
>> I can You're passionate about it.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. I love it.
>> You won't see what these guys. I mean,
how fast.
>> So, we just spawned in a drift track.
>> Ah, let's go.
>> Okay. So, you you want to tell them what
we're doing right now?
>> Well, we're going to drift. I hope
you're not going to kill me if I'm going
to be in the car, but I saw you're a
professional, so I think it should be
cool.
>> So, this right here is like a full drift
track. We could basically do whatever we
want pretty much.
>> Yes. Try not to not to smash [laughter]
the car. Okay.
>> Okay. So, so you you won't get stomach
sick. I can hit donuts. You'll be good.
>> Do whatever.
>> Who's calling that [__] [music] Who's
calling that [__] Who's calling that
[__]
>> [music]
>> Is it?
Is it?
Is it party? Where the fun? Where
[music] the [__] the fun? Where the [__]
the fun
[music]
baby girl?
>> Car boys. Good morning. It is currently
5:30 in the morning Dubai time. So, I
don't typically get up at this time, but
Saman hit me up. He's like, "Yo, you
should pull up. We're going to fish
today in the morning." So, it's Saturday
morning. So, these guys really get up at
5 in the morning every single day. No,
they get up like at 4. And I said,
"Okay, you know what? [__] it. I'm
down." So, we're pulling up to his house
now. We're going to fish and get some
other things planned. So, let's see what
we do.
>> Life is too good to be asleep, man.
>> I can tell. I'm like, "All right, even
on a Saturday, [__] it. Let's get
>> it." Let's get it. What What you
thought? We said we go fishing.
>> I'm down. There's actually fish out
here.
>> Yeah,
>> like like big fish that you can catch.
Okay, you guys know
>> you're going to eat them after.
>> Okay, I'm Cuban. I know how to fish. I'm
pretty decent. I don't know how we're
going to pull out a shark with this
[__] but let's see. [laughter]
>> Bro, we we are we are viral. We can do
what the [__] we want.
>> You know what, brother? Trust me, I'm
I'm going to be like, "Yo,
>> bare hands if you needed to be."
>> I will be I I'll grab the tail. You can
grab the front, you know,
>> right? We just fight with it, you know?
Hey, but for sure guys, this is a
privilege that you can all witness this.
You know, first time you see Anua
brother's fish and we also got my man
Alex here. Where the [__] do you see
that?
>> Neighbors should be waking up to to
witness this. [laughter]
>> So, if we don't catch a fish, we're not
eating today pretty much.
>> Exactly.
>> You might be close.
Feels
like there's nobody out here, bro.
>> It's kind of the benefit of waking up at
5:00 a.m.
>> This time I'm usually
>> snoring.
>> But what time you normally wake up?
>> It depends if I have to stay up to trade
or if I have to get up to trade. It
really depends.
>> Until what time you normally stay up to
trade?
>> Like 3, 4. Or if I fall asleep like at
12:00, I wake up at 7.
>> So what's the best time for trading in
the US? In the US, 1 in the morning.
>> 1 in the morning.
>> Yeah. And then you're up all night. So,
it's it's pretty shitty. Trading here
has been the best.
>> Really?
>> Yeah. Oh, literally the best.
>> Swing trade.
>> Swing. Swing. Trade the [__]
[__] out of this.
>> I didn't even see where it went.
>> You caught 30 fish here.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. So, you Okay. Like there's
actually fish. No,
>> you're not here fishing. If we're not
[laughter]
confident, we should for sure catch
something.
>> Catch something. Okay.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> 3 hours later.
>> Looks like we're going to have to fast.
You ever do like a 2, three day fast?
>> I've done like water fast, juice fast.
>> For how long?
>> 3 days. I only do it if I need a detox.
You
>> I've done two days. 3 days.
>> Yeah.
>> Just straight water.
>> Yeah. You just lose too much muscle.
That's what I don't like.
>> Yeah. No, I don't do it now. I did one
when I came out of jail. three-day fast
cuz I was eating so much chicken and
rice and dirty things inside just felt
dirty.
>> Yeah. So, you wanted to cleanse all that
out.
>> Yeah. I I really wanted to cleanse but
also when you come out of jail you're uh
you're a different person, you know.
>> Do you feel comfortable already or not
yet?
>> Now fully.
>> Yeah.
>> First month. No.
>> No.
>> People think you step out and you're
like partying dancing on the table. It's
not like that. You know, you you come
out, you're relieved, but at the same
time, your mind is still kind of in the
jail mode, fully war zone, fight or
flight. You are paranoid.
>> You got into any fights in there or not?
>> There were big fights every day at some
point during Ramadan especially. Bro,
I've seen people get stabbed with pens
and and things like that.
>> But you never got into a fight?
>> No, we had we had some stuff happening,
but bro, I have a security guard with
me.
>> So, you had security in jail?
>> I had security in jail with me. I got
arrested with my security, my chef. I
got the full on team. Boom. Come in, me,
my brother, security with you, like huge
as [__] chef with you, running around
trying to make food, you know, while
[laughter] you have no no ways to make
food. One microwave for 200 people. So,
he was fighting at the microwave line.
My bus got to eat. My bus got to eat,
>> you know. It was funny as [__]
>> Oh, that that that that's a cool story.
>> You were in there teamed up.
>> Teamed up fully
>> past 1, 2005. Sorry. Market's about to
open. We're in the forefront of it.
First in line. No, everybody's sleeping.
Sleeping on the opportunity. Waking up
and catching your own success. Catching
your own food. All these people are
probably sleeping because they're so
rich they could just go buy it.
>> Maybe they're probably sleeping cuz they
know there's no fish here.
>> That's probably Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. There it
is. There it is. If we don't catch
something now, we're [__]
>> [__] Oh, I see him right there.
>> Yeah. No. Come on.
>> Come on, boys.
>> That's how we do it.
>> Yes, sir.
>> [__] [laughter]
>> [__] Yo, we're all eating
today. All right. All of us. Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah. I think I caught two of these
[__]
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, [__] NO. [laughter]
>> [__] How the [__] does [laughter]
How the [__] Nah. Yo. Yo. Look, look,
look. My lure got [__] up. [laughter]
>> That's That's a rare,
>> bro. How the [__] [laughter]
[__]
>> In forex terms, can you explain the your
take on the situation?
>> We got diddy. We got wicked out of the
[__] market right now. Wow. What a
teacher. Trade almost hit take profit.
Came back and took us out of stop loss.
>> Oh yeah. Come on. No. Yeah.
>> Oh, this this No. No. [laughter]
No. Holy [__] I've never seen one of
these before. I know. You can lift them
up through the back. Yeah. Like
>> you can touch them on this side over
here and nothing.
>> No, I will not do it.
>> Is it?
>> [__] hell.
>> Oh, you got
it.
>> Yeah, a little bit. Yeah. Could I
squeeze it? No, but that shit's 100%
alive. Chef doesn't know how to cook
that up. [laughter]
>> Cook jelly.
>> Well, shout out to you guys for feeding
us, you know. Thank you guys.
>> At least we're eating.
>> Okay.
>> I'll uh I'll put the seasoning on it.
[music]
>> I brought you guys a gift. Just just
like a small gift, some love. I want to
give to you guys.
>> I I I also have a gift. I will grab you.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Okay. That's crazy. It's a little It's a
little gesture. I don't know. I see that
we have a lot of things in common and I
think that it would fit you guys. the
Bugatti.
[laughter]
>> This This gift this one's for you.
>> Thank you. Thank you.
>> And then this one is for you.
>> Appreciate it, bro.
>> And this one's for like both of you guys
together, right? So, this is kind of
like a gift for both of you. You guys
>> should leave it or open it or open you
guys can open it now.
>> I think it kind of fits you guys
perfect. Bro, I was trying to get these
guys a gift. It took me I think we were
walking through the mall for like 3
hours, bro. I couldn't figure out what
to get you guys.
>> It's difficult to give guys like us
gifts. I I went to Prada to get you guys
something from Prada. But
>> this is sick. This is sick.
>> A Hermes Astray.
>> Sick astray, man. Smoke. So good.
Cigarette.
>> You like exotic stuff supposedly.
>> I love it, man. Exotic.
>> This is This is my color, man.
>> And I know you like blue. So good cuz
the interior of the road. That's for
you, bro.
>> I I know you're a man who already has it
all, but this is one thing that by far
made me the the most money in business.
So
>> yeah,
>> you you you'll love this one.
>> This is for you. What does it say?
>> I don't know. It's just [snorts]
packaging, but [laughter] you have to
look inside.
>> Okay, let me see. So, this is what's
made you the most amount of money.
>> Yeah.
>> Wow. Who the formula to achieve bigger
goals?
>> Who not? How? Yeah.
>> So the the concept basically explains
the fact that instead of every time you
want to do or achieve something or do
something new for your business, instead
of how do I do this, you change it to
who can do this because there are always
people already walked the path and since
I applied this in business everything
exploded and now we got companies with a
couple hundred employees um you know
>> autopilot even from prison you know we
were zero involved with the business
till the business
was killing it.
>> And it's because of all this concept
because we have the right who's around
us, you know. So,
>> all right. Appreciate it. Thank you.
>> Thank you. Let's quickly check what we
got here.
>> Oh, yeah. So, this is like another
little detail for both of you guys. I
know you guys are African and uh this is
a oneofone African Dupont lighter.
>> A This is sick. I've heard of it.
>> Yeah. That is like irreplaceable. You
will never find another one.
>> How does do these work? I think uh
I need to fill up.
>> They had no gas.
>> So this is your your your gifts are on
point. Your gift game.
>> I try my best.
>> Your professional cigar smoker or
>> we should get some cigars and smoke
later. But we just got to fill up that
with gas. But that is like extremely
rare. We have no
All right, boys. We are here in Bugatti
of Dubai. I I actually want to get like
something for myself for the house. So,
I don't know if they have like cool
gifts cuz the Bugatti in Miami is pretty
whack. There's really like nothing
there. Maybe they have like cool things
here that I'll take to the house like a
actual Bugatti car. I've had two
Bugattis and I've never actually own one
of those like demo cars cuz I've never
bought it from the Bugatti factory. So,
pretty cool. The door door is pretty
sick.
My [__] is
man. That's crazy. I had that exact same
super sport and I had that little old
vintage car. I don't know if you can see
it right there. See, like that's some
[__] that I'd want. Like I'd probably go
in there and just buy that like one of
those demo cars, but no Bugatti store.
L in the chat. I thought we were going
to be able to even test drive a Bugatti.
You think they'd let me test drive it?
>> Yeah. Right.
I look like a guy that could afford a
Bugatti, you know.
>> All right, ladies and gentlemen. Today
we have a very special podcast. None
other than the man himself, Alex
Gonzalez.
>> Bro, I'm going to save this.
>> Yeah, that's it.
>> Thank you very much, man.
>> I hope you like your questions.
>> Yeah, that was good, bro.
>> Bro, I got you something.
>> Oh [__] bro. I should have got you
something.
>> No, bro. No, bro. This is a terrible
bag.
>> I I brought it in this so I can hide it
from you.
>> Oh, man. Guys, I I don't know what to
say. Check it out. I don't know if you
like it, but this is the first video.
All right, let's check it out. I open
it.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Guys, we just got a gift. Oh, wow. Oh my
good. Bro,
>> do do you have an Hermes?
>> I don't I don't have anything from
Hammers, guys. What is this? A blanket?
>> Yeah. Yeah. This like a proper Hermes
blanket. This is like
>> Yo, I'm going to be sleeping rich today,
guys. [laughter]
Anything bad I said in that podcast is
getting cut out. You know, this is this
is bribery, guys. I didn't find this
out. Oh, no. Thank you. I appreciate it.
Thank you.
>> I got you.
>> This I have to say this is probably the
most expensive gift I've got in a while,
[laughter]
guys. I'm going to keep it right here.
>> This This has to get like washed like a
like like a specific way.
>> I can feel the fabric. Like I feel like
>> this is like proper material. This is
like This is what like the bougie people
have in their homes, bro. I don't even
have this in my
>> I want to be sleeping, bro. Honestly, I
don't even want to ask the price tag.
>> Heras slippers are like a couple grand,
let alone like they probably charge by
the square, you know.
>> Set and forget, brother.
>> Set and forget, bro. This guy,
>> he's a legend.
>> Let's head back to Miami.
>> Let's go. Thank you. Thank you, my
brother. I appreciate. [__] I feel bad.
I I should He came to my house. This is
crazy. [music]
Heat. [music]